[
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is correct?",
        "answeroption": {
            "a": "jQuery is a JSON Library",
            "b": "jQuery is a JavaScript Library"
        },
        "correctanswer": "jQuery is a JavaScript Library",
        "incorrect": false
    },
    {
        "question": "jQuery uses CSS selectors to select elements?",
        "answeroption": {
            "a": "false",
            "b": "true"
        },
        "correctanswer": "true",
        "incorrect": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sign does jQuery use as a shortcut for jQuery?",
        "answeroption": {
            "a": "the ? sign",
            "b": "the % sign",
            "c": "the $ sign"
        },
        "correctanswer": "the $ sign",
        "incorrect": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Look at the following selector: $('div'). What does it select?",
        "answeroption": {
            "a": "All div elements",
            "b": "The first div element"
        },
        "correctanswer": "All div elements",
        "incorrect": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Is jQuery a library for client scripting or server scripting?",
        "answeroption": {
            "a": "Client scripting",
            "b": "Server scripting"
        },
        "correctanswer": "Client scripting",
        "incorrect": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it possible to use jQuery together with AJAX?",
        "answeroption": {
            "a": "No",
            "b": "Yes"
        },
        "correctanswer": "Yes",
        "incorrect": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The jQuery html() method works for both HTML and XML documents",
        "answeroption": {
            "a": "False",
            "b": "True"
        },
        "correctanswer": "False",
        "incorrect": false
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the correct jQuery code to set the background color of all p elements to red?",
        "answeroption": {
            "a": "$('p').layout('background-color','red');",
            "b": "$('p').manipulate('background-color','red');",
            "c": "$('p').css('background-color','red');",
            "d": "$('p').style('background-color','red');"
        },
        "correctanswer": "$('p').css('background-color','red');",
        "incorrect": false
    },
    {
        "question": "With jQuery, look at the following selector: $('div.intro'). What does it select?",
        "answeroption": {
            "a": "The first div element with id='intro'",
            "b": "All div elements with id='intro'",
            "c": "All div elements with class='intro'",
            "d": "The first div element with class='intro'"
        },
        "correctanswer": "All div elements with class='intro'",
        "incorrect": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Which jQuery method is used to hide selected elements?",
        "answeroption": {
            "a": "hidden()",
            "b": "hide()",
            "c": "display(none)",
            "d": "visible(false)"
        },
        "correctanswer": "hide()",
        "incorrect": false
    }

]